

#### CONTACT

**PHONE** +4917664209354

# **EMAIL** franko.safradin13@gmail.com







#### **HARD SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Node.is
- React.js
- Next.js
- Git
- MongoDB
- Responsive Design
- Laptop and PC repairement

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Intercultural competences
- Presentation skills
- Self-marketing
- Analitical thinking
- Flexibility
- Team building & team work
- SCRUM

#### **LANGUAGE**

- English (C1)
- German (B2)
- Croatian (Native)

### **FRANKO SAFRADIN**

#### WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Open-minded and hardworking person, currently located in Düsseldorf, always on the hunt for new knowledge, which will benefit me and the people around me. New to the development industry, but ready to learn from more experienced colleagues, and also to teach those who are less experienced than

#### **EDUCATION**

### DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH November 2021 - November 2022

- Enrolled in one-year long web development course
- Learned and studied technologies that enabled me to create full-stack applications
- Learned technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, and MongoDB)
- Graduated a Bootcamp with final MERN project
- In-depth knowledge of soft skills

### Zagreb University of Applied Sciences September 2012 - ?

- Enrolled in IT university
- Studied algorithms, web development, and computer science
- Relevant Coursework: Mathematics (I and II), Typography, Media and Photography, basic OOP

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

## Housekeeper InterContinental Düsseldorf | 12/2018-12/2020

- Supervised cleaning service workers
- Provided high-end customer service
- Worked in a fast-paced, international, multicultural company

### Front Office/Receptionist Suncani Hvar d.d Hvar | 05/2017-08/2018

- Fulfilling guest wishes, providing high-end stay
- Sharpened my MS Office and Hotelsoftware skills

### PC repair technician Komping d.o.o Vitez | 11/2015-03/2017

- Repairing PC Hardware (Motherboards, speakers, graphic cards)
- Installing and troubleshooting Windows 8 and other company software

#### Ecommerce Coordinator Frizerland Vitez | 02/2014-09/2015

- Updating, adding, and fixing products on an e-commerce website.
- Contact the clients, and prepare products for shipment.